Speaking of Golden Week Featured Gourmet Festivals
Today we came to eat dumplings!
We came to eat gyoza!
This is the third year for the festival to be held in Komazawa Park
Craft Gyoza Festival
Popular gyoza restaurants from all over Japan gather here!
You can enjoy 28 kinds of menu!
You can compare 4 kinds of gyoza skewers from Kanagawa
Saitama's pink-colored plump shrimp dumplings
A5 rank Saga Gyoza from Saitama, and more!
Today, we'll check out some of the popular restaurants at the Gyoza Festival!
Long queue in the hot weather was at Gyoza no Miyadenden!
The appearance of the gyoza was so impressive!
Very round and cute!
Lots of cheese!
Looks delicious!
The reason why they are so popular is not only because of their appearance.
When you eat it, you can feel the juices of the meat.
The juices bursting out of the meat and the juices bursting out of the meat.
In order to lock in the juices, we made the crust thicker
We wrapped it so that it becomes round and round
The inside is filled with simmered vegetables
so the juices overflow like this!
What's more
Cheddar cheese is sprinkled on the top to create a rich harmony with the juices.
You can enjoy the rich harmony of the juices and the meat.
The richness of the cheddar cheese and the juices overflowing from the meat are a perfect match.
When you try it, you will be surprised at how chewy the crust is!
The rich cheese and juicy meat juices intertwine in your mouth!
This is Marco's Gyoza Specialty!
It was the first time for me to discover and enjoy the dumplings at Marco's Gyoza Specialty!
A lot of grated yam on top of the gyoza!
And the dumplings are made of tapioca flour.
The dumplings are made with tapioca flour for the skin.
so you can enjoy the sticky texture of the dumpling.
After baking them until crispy
After grilling them to a crisp, we pour grated yam over them and sprinkle salt from the sea-ear dashi broth on top.
so that you can feel the umami flavor of the dumpling.
The starchy sauce is filled with shibaebi (shrimp) and pork.
How does it taste?
Delicious!
You can feel the fluffy yam and the umami of the broth.
It is juicy, but the yam makes it refreshing to eat!
The dumplings and wine, the skin and the bean paste are all edible.
It has a new texture with a crispy surrounding.
It is a fried gyoza with a crispy texture.
It's hot and full of juices from the meat
I was confident because when I chewed it, the juices came out
The bean paste is based on Tokachi's beef and
It is blended with white miso and sakura miso and enriched with butter
The sauce is made with red wine vinegar to add a sourness that makes these fried gyoza unique!
The skin is crispy and the bean paste is well seasoned and juicy!
The coconara miso goes well with the dumplings.
Please subscribe to our channel for more information.